{
    "id": "f80d7f9ce2a64a20adc3565024b84ce2",
    "title": "For, Since, In And From",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I once studied the piano …………………… three years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7bb8cdcd0e9433ab79e29504964f62f"
        },
        {
            "question": "That house has been empty ………………….. two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbb32a8c69534c059a94a887ed96a6d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known her ………………… a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fdb39983c0704088ba0680e3dded8bc5"
        },
        {
            "question": "We go away …………………. three weeks every summer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9121c1dd44514c7ba2e2170e67a3c491"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long are you here ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "87fbe50493eb4427a2e60e6d1b8f82ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the worst storm …………………. years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b0170a08b594da4bfccc4397eb685cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be here ………………….. four o’clock onwards.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "213884fb6640403abc97d0a878efc7e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I work …………………. nine to five.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "78153c21d9ed42ed84a73ee9958ed7e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known her ………………….. three days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4e324d720e142d19b9423edb8b395f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… the dawn of civilization, people have made war.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "From",
                "since",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb29035118db4b61b2b45a986de86a17"
        }
    ]
}